Guide to the Peter Salovey, President of Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the president, 2012-2018; Accession 2019-A-0015
  - Chronological Files
    - Part IV, 2013 October 18 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Part V, 2013 October 23-2013 October 25 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Part VI, 2013 October 25 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Part I, 2013 November 1 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Part II, 2013 November 8 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Part III, 2013 November 8-2013 November 15 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Part IV (folder 1 of 2), 2013 November 22 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Part IV (folder 2 of 2), 2013 November 22 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Part I, 2013 December 1-2013 December 6 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Part II, 2013 December 6 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Part III, 2013 December 9-2013 December 13 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Part IV, 2013 December 13 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Part V, 2013 December 13 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Part VI, 2013 December 18-2013 December 20 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Part I, 2014 January 3-2014 January 8 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Part II, 2014 January 10 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Part III, 2014 January 10 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Part IV, 2014 January 16-2014 January 17 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Part VIII, 2014 January 31 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Part IX, 2014 January 31 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Part I, 2014 February 7 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Part II, 2014 February 7 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Part III, 2014 February 11-2014 February 14 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Part IV, 2014 February 17-2014 February 21 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Part V, 2014 February 21 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Part VI, 2014 February 21-2014 February 28 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Part VII, 2014 February 28 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Part I, 2014 March 3-2014 March 7 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Part II, 2014 March 13-2014 March 21 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Part III, 2014 March 13-2014 March 21 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Part IV, 2014 March 21 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Park V, 2014 March 21-2014 March 28 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Part VI Asia Development Council, 2014 March 28 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Part VII Asia Development Council, 2014 March 28 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Part VIII Asia Development Council, 2014 March 28 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Part I, 2014 April 2-2014 April 4 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Part II, 2014 April 11 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Part III (folder 1 of 2), 2014 April 17 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Part III (folder 2 of 2), 2014 April 17 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Part IV, 2014 April 25 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Part I, 2014 May 2 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Part II, 2014 May 9 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Part III, 2014 May 12-2014 May 16 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Part IIIa, 2014 May 16 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Part IV, 2014 May 23 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Part IVa, 2014 May 23 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Part V, 2014 May 28-2014 May 30 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Part Va, 2014 May 30 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Part I, 2014 June 6 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Part Ia, 2014 June 6 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Part II, 2014 June 13 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Part IIa, 2014 June 13 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Part III, 2014 June 20 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Part IIIa, 2014 June 20 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Part I, 2014 July 7-2014 July 11 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Part II, 2014 July 11 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Part III, 2014 July 11 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Part IV, 2014 July 11 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Part V, 2014 July 11 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Part VI, 2014 July 18 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Part VII, 2014 July 25 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Part VIII, 2014 July 25 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Part I, 2014 August 8 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Part II, 2014 August 8 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Part III, 2014 August 15 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Part IV, 2014 August 22 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Part V, 2014 August 22 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Part VI, 2014 August 29 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Part I, 2014 September 5 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Part II, 2014 September 12 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Part III, 2014 September 19 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Part IV, 2014 September 19 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Part V (1 of 2), 2014 September 26 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Part V (2 of 2), 2014 September 26 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Part I, 2014 October 3 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Part II, 2014 October 10 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Part III, 2014 October 17 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Part IV (1 of 2), 2014 October 24 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Part V (2 of 2), 2014 October 24 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Part VI, 2014 October 31 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Part VII, 2014 October 31 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Part I, 2014 November 7 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Part II, 2014 November 14 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Part III (1 of 2), 2014 November 21 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Part III (1 of 2), 2014 November 21 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Part I, 2014 December 5 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Part II, 2014 December 12 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Part III, 2014 December 12 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Part IV, 2014 December 19 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Part V, 2014 December 19 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Part VI, 2014 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Corporation (Yale)
    - Action Items Notes, 2013 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Appointments Announcements, 2013 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Appointments Chairs and Masters, 2013 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Ed Bass Notes, 2013 April 2 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Breakfast Executive Session, 2014 February 21 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Clinical Trials at Yale, 2013 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Commencement Weekend Schedule, 2013 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Commencement Weekend Schedule, 2014 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Conversations with President, Provost and Corporation: "Setting the Agenda", 2014 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Executive Session Agenda, 2013 April 5 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Fall Retreat, 2013 September 26 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Fall Retreat, 2014 October 9 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Fall Strategic Planning Retreat, 2013 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Fall Strategic Planning Retreat, 2014-15 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Fellows Handbook, 2012-13 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Finance Committee, 2012 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Long-Range Planning, 2014 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Marshall Article, 2013 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Meet Yale's 23rd Event 6 November, 2013 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Meeting Minutes
      - 2013 December 6 (Box 19, Folder 27)
      - 2013 December 6 (Box 19, Folder 28)
      - 2013 December 6 (Box 19, Folder 29)
      - 2014 February 21 (Box 19, Folder 30)
      - 2014 February 21 (Box 19, Folder 31)
      - 2014 April 3 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - 2014 April 3 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - 2014 April 3 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - 2014 May 18 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - 2014 May 18 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - 2014 May 18 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - 2014 October 10 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - 2014 December 12 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Meetings Scheduled Dates, 2013 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Named Chair Suggestions, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Naming Residential Colleges, 2013 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - New Fellow Orientation (folder 1 of 3), 2013 August 7 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - New Fellow Orientation (folder 2 of 3), 2013 August 7 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - New Fellow Orientation (folder 3 of 3), 2013 August 7 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - New Fellow Orientation, 2014 September 17 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Planning, 2013 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - President's Agenda Supplemental Materials (folder 1 of 2), 2014 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - President's Agenda Supplemental Materials (folder 2 of 2), 2014 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Rehearsals, 2013 November 6 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Retreat Plenary on the future of Higher Education, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Retreat Planning Reviews, 2014-2015 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Senior Fellow Planning Meeting, 2014 June 4 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Senior Fellow Retreat, 2013 June 3 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Senior Fellow Selection Process Notes, 2013 February 13 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Special Topics Meeting, 2012 June 4 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Takeaways, 2012 December 7 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Takeaways and followups, 2013 February 22 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Yale College Council Mid-Year Report, 2013 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Foundations
    - Yale Africa Initiative Scholarship Fund Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Yale Alumni Fund Board Meeting, 2014 September 19 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Fundraising Yale Alumni Fund Correspondence, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Yale Alumni Fund filming, 2013 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - American Psychological Foundation Correspondence, 2013 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - American Psychological Foundation Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Bartlesville Community Foundation Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Bio-Medical Research Fund Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - JP Morgan Chase Correspondence, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Bill, Hillary and Chelsea Clinton Foundation Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Columbus Citizens Foundation Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Community Foundation for Greater New Haven Correspondence, 2013 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Community Foundation for Greater New Haven Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Community Foundation for Greater New Haven Correspondence and Publications, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Community Health Network Foundation Annual Report, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Jack Kent Cooke Foundation Correspondence, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Cowles Foundation Directorship, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Daniels Fund Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Arthur Vining Davis Foundation Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Davis Educational Foundation Correspondence, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Jessie Ball duPont Fund Correspondence, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Jessie Ball duPont Fund Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Freedom from Religion Foundation Corresponcence, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Friends of Yale Africa Scholarship Fund Correspondence, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Funacion Botin Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Fundacion Botin Report, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Goizueto Foundation Grant Agreement, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Horace W Goldsmith Foundation Correspondence, 2012-2014 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Horace W Goldsmith Foundation Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Warren M. Goodspeed Scholarship Fund Correspondence, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Gruber Foundation Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Harris Foundation Fellowship, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Harris Foundation Correspondence, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Ho-Am Foundation Prize Committee Correspondence, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Kavli Foundation Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Kavli Foundation Visit 16 September, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Henry Luce Foundation Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Edward Mallinckrodt, Jr. Foundation Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Andrew W. Mellon Foundation Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Andrew W. Mellon Foundation Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Andrew W. Mellon Foundation Proposal, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Moffatt Fund Provost and Development Meeting, 2013 October 22 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - National Science Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - National Science Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - National Science Survey, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Nuclear Age Peace Foundation Correspondence, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - ONE Campaign Correspondence, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - David and Lucile Packard Foundation Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - David and Lucile Packard Foundation Fellows Nomination, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Virginia G Piper Charitable Trust Correspondence, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Posse Foundation Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Robina Foundation Dinner, 2014 March 4 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Robina Foundation Visit Crane Meeting Notes, 2014 February 17 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Rockefeller Foundation Correspondence, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Rockefeller Foundation Grants and Contracts Extension Request, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Carnelia Coswell Rossi Foundation Correspondence, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Spencer Foundation Correspondence, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Tree of Life Educational Fund Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - United Health Foundation Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - US Sciences Po Foundation Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Government
    - Federal
      - Air Force and Naval Reserve Officers' Training Corps at Yale Summary, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 43)
      - Army Senior Reserve Officers' Training Corp Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 44)
      - Budget Appropriations Outlook and Analysis, 2013-2014 (Box 21, Folder 45)
      - Cabranes Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 21, Folder 46)
      - College Opportunity for Low-Income Student Report, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 47)
      - Congress Esty, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 48)
      - Congress Lee Notes, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 49)
      - Congress Smith Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 21, Folder 50)
      - Department of Defense Voluntary Education Partnership Memorandum of Understanding, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 51)
      - Department of Education Clery Act, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 52)
      - Department of Education Correspondence, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 53)
      - Department of Education Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 54)
      - Department of Education Equity in Athletics Disclosure Act, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 55)
      - Department of Education Student Aid Approval, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 56)
      - Department of Education Title IV, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 57)
      - Department of Education Undersecretary Mitchell, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 58)
      - Department of Labor Statistics Employment Lost Index, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 59)
      - Department of Veterans Affairs Correspondence, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 60)
      - Department of Veterans Affairs Yellow Ribbon Program, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 61)
      - Former Presidents Carter Correspondence, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 62)
      - Former Presidents Carter Visit, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 63)
      - Franklin Project McCrystal, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 64)
      - Grant and Contract Expenditures Spreadsheet, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 65)
      - House of Representatives Clymer Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 66)
      - Naval Reserve Officers' Training Corps Correspondence, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 67)
      - Navy Admiral Richardson visit, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 68)
      - Northeast Delegation Reverse Sequester Letter, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 69)
      - Office of Mangement and Budget Director Donovan, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 70)
      - Office of Science and Technology Policy, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 71)
      - President Obama Call to Action, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 72)
      - President Obama Correspondence, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 73)
      - President Obama Plan to Rate Colleges, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 74)
      - Reserve Officers' Training Corps Air Force and Navy at Yale 2012-2013, 2015 (Box 21, Folder 75)
      - Reserve Officers' Training Corp President's Review Ceremony, 2015 April 30 (Box 21, Folder 76)
      - Science and Education Advocacy Correspondence, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 77)
      - Secretary of State Clinton Visit, 2013 October 5 (Box 21, Folder 78)
      - Secretary of State Kerry Notes, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 79)
      - Senate Blumenthal Correspondence, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 80)
      - Senate Brown Correspondence, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 81)
      - Senate Crisco Correspondence, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 82)
      - Senate Murphy Background, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 83)
      - Senate Murphy Correspondence, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 84)
      - Senate Portman, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 85)
      - Senate Warner Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 86)
      - Sumission Success Rates Spreadsheets, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 87)
      - Supreme Court Justice Breyer, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 88)
      - Supreme Court Justice Marshall, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 89)
      - Supreme Court Justice Sotomayor Correspondence, 2015 (Box 21, Folder 90)
      - White House Biographies, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 91)
      - White House Commitments, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 92)
      - White House Visit 16 January, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 93)
      - White House Task Force to Protect Students from Sexual Assault Report, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 94)
      - Yale vs Army Brunch, 2014 September 27 (Box 21, Folder 95)
    - Local Government
      - Mayor DeStefano Correspondence and notes, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 96)
      - Mayor Harp Inauguration, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 97)
      - Mayor Harp Photographs, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 98)
      - New Haven Arts, Culture and Tourism Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 99)
      - New Haven Board of Alders Businesses Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 21, Folder 100)
      - New Haven Board of Police Commissioners Complaint, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 101)
      - New Haven Community Development, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 102)
      - New Haven Department of Assessment Correspondence, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 103)
      - New Haven East Midtown Rezoning, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 104)
      - New Haven Future Project Correspondence, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 105)
    - State Governments
      - Congresswoman DeLauro Champion of Science Reception, 2013 January 31 (Box 21, Folder 106)
      - Connecticut Relations Discussion Notes, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 107)
      - Connecticut Office of Higher Education Correspondence, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 108)
      - Connecticut Office of Higher Education Teacher Quality Partnership Grant Program, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 109)
      - Governor Malloy Correspondence, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 110)
      - Governor Malloy Meeting Notes, 2013 November 19 (Box 21, Folder 111)
      - Kentucky Colonel Appointment Salovey, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 112)
  - Other Universities
    - University of Alabama Correspondence, 2012-2014 (Box 21, Folder 113)
    - University of Arizona Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 114)
    - University of Baltimore Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 115)
    - University of Bergen Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 116)
    - Bogazici Correspondence, 2015 (Box 21, Folder 117)
    - Boston University Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 118)
    - Brown University Paxon Notes, 2015 March 19 (Box 21, Folder 119)
    - University of California at Berkeley Inaugural Address, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 120)
    - University of California Hastings College of the Law Correspondence, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 121)
    - University of Cambridge Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 122)
    - Carnegie Mellon University Correspondence, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 123)
    - Central South University Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 124)
    - Chinese University of Hong Kong Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 125)
    - Chinese University of Hong Kong Honorary Degree Ceremony, 2013 January 15 (Box 21, Folder 126)
    - University of Cincinnati Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 127)
    - City University of New York Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 128)
    - Clemson University Correspondence, 2013-2015 (Box 21, Folder 129)
    - Colgate University Correspondence, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 130)
    - University of Connecticut Jackson Laboratory for General Medicine Memorandum of Understanding, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 131)
    - University of Connecticut Publication, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 132)
    - Cornell University Journal of Law and Public Policy, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 133)
    - Dartmouth College President Hanlon visit, 2013 November 13 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Dartmouth College Presidential Summit Remarks, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Dhirubhai Ambani Internation School Correspondence, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Drexel Univesity Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - East Carolina University Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - University of Edinburgh Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - ETH Zurich Swiss Federal Institute of Technology Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Ewha Women's University Correspondence, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Universidad de Extremo Sul Catarinense Correspondence, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - University of Florence Psychology, Emotions and Research (PER) Lab, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Fairfield Univesity Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Fudan University Correspondence, 2013-2015 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Fudan University Visit and Delegation, 2015 February 9 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Garissa University College Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Hague Institute for Global Justice Correspondence, 2015 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Harvard Graduate School of Education Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Harvard University President Faust Speech, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Haverford College Correspondence, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - University of Hong Kong Visiting International Student Program, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Hunan University of Arts and Science Correspondence, 2015 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Johns Hopkins School of Advanced International Studies, 2011 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - University of Illinois at Urbana Champaign Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Indiana University Correspondence, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Institute of Science and Technology Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - International College of Angiology Annual World Congress, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Jawaharlal Nehru University, 2013-2014 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Jindal Global University Vice Chancellor Kumar Meeting, 2015 January 27 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST) Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Korea University Salovey Photograph, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - University of Jordan Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Juilliard Correspondence, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Kasetsart University Correspondence, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Lahore University of Management, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - L'Ecole Namale Superieure Correspondence, 2015 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Lehigh University Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Lycoming College Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - University of Maryland Baltimore County Correspondence, 2012-2014 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - University of Massachusetts Boston Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - University of Massachusetts Lowell Correspondence, 2015 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology Inaugural Address, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - University of Michigan Board of Regents Retreat 16 January, 2013-2014 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - University of Michigan Institute for Research on Innovation and Science, 2015 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Moravian College Correspondence, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Mount Holyoke College Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - National Institute of Development Administration Correspondence, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - National Tsing Hua University Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 47)